comcastoffers.com 2007-12-17

# Comcast High-Speed Internet: Privacy Policy

Effective June 2004

**Comcastoffers.com is committed to protecting your privacy.**

This Privacy Policy will provide information to you regarding how we collect and use your personal information, and about choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to address new issues or changes to our practices. These changes will be posted here so that you will always know our privacy policies. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically to see if there have been any revisions.

Comcastoffers.com is a Web site independently operated by Broadbandoffers.com under license by Comcast Corporation. Some offers brought to you by Comcastoffers.com are not available directly from Comcast Corporation.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please send us an e-mail at [comcastprivacy@customerservicesite.com](mailto:comcastprivacy@customerservicesite.com) or write to us at the following address:

> **Comcastoffers.com**  
>  1555 Sherman Avenue  
>  Box 310   
>  Evanston, Illinois   
>  60201   
>  ATTN: Director of Technology

**Scope of Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy applies to Comcastoffers.com's method of collection and use of information gathered by us for the customers that we serve on http://www.comcastoffers.com (the "Web Site"). However, please note that the privacy practices of Comcast Corporation are not covered by this Privacy Policy. In addition, once you leave our Web Site via a link or otherwise, this Privacy Policy does not apply and Comcastoffers.com is not responsible for how data and information obtained from you on other Web sites is used by the operators of such Web sites.

**Security**  
We believe that protecting the security of your Personal Information is very important. Therefore, we have put strong security measures in place to attempt to protect your Personal Information. Access to Personal Information is limited to Comcastoffers.com employees or other authorized individuals, and a limited number of our fulfillment partners. Identities are verified by internal network access rules and application username/password pairs. Data fields that identify individuals are separated from non-sensitive data fields. Data identifying Personal Information is encrypted through use of industry-standard AES encryption methods and practices. Data decryption keys are kept physically separate from encryption keys and encrypted data. Records are marked with tamper-proof authentication digests.

Comcastoffers.com requires internal users to use Comcastoffers.com's standardized methods of data transfer, encryption and storage. We encourage external parties, service providers and vendors to use our standardized methods of data transfer, encryption and storage, or an equivalent method.

We also monitor hardware and software logs for operational compliance with security policies. Comcastoffers.com quarantines data that arrives on a channel not approved in the policy until its source and disposition can be determined in accordance with the security policy. Consequences of non-compliance range from delay in reporting response times to refusal to accept or verify data, in accordance with penalties specified by contract. 

Barriers erected to prevent potential breaches of secure information include a sophisticated security system, internal audits, internal policies/procedures and a daily backup of all information. The Director of Technology is responsible for all aspects of secure information within Comcastoffers.com.

No service provider/vendor/external party should be able to decrypt the encrypted data of any other service provider/vendor/external party should data be misdelivered.

**Enforcement**  
Comcastoffers.com monitors data center metrics on approximately a weekly basis. Network vulnerability testing and standard NOC monitoring are provided by the data center administration staff, with options for performing third-party security audits on demand.

Comcastoffers.com performs full recovery tests prior to live deployment of a new application or server system. Comcastoffers.com performs recovery tests of backup media on a monthly to quarterly schedule to assure that existing backup regimes have created working recovery sets.

Comcastoffers.com actively monitors current and upcoming regulatory and compliance issues through outside legal resources.

**Information Collected by Comcastoffers.com**  
Personal information ("Personal Information") may include the following:

  * name
  * address
  * e-mail address
  * phone number(s)
  * credit card number and expiration date
  * computer system specs
  * gender (optional)
  * age (optional)

Comcastoffers.com uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all Web pages where Personal Information is required. When entering Personal Information, we strongly recommend an SSL-enabled Web browser. We do not store credit card numbers on our servers after you enter your credit card information on the Comcastoffers.com Web site. This information is only used to confirm your identity and we do not have access to your personal financial data. Transacting online with Comcastoffers.com will not open your credit card information to dissemination. Comcastoffers.com does not disclose, sell, trade, rent, or otherwise reveal credit card information to any third parties.

We may request Personal Information from you in connection with your use of, or participation in, the Web Site, including applications, registrations, suggestions or requests for additional information, or in connection with other services or resources provided on or through the Web Site. Personal Information is collected and stored on servers owned and maintained by a third party and leased to Comcastoffers.com exclusively. A confidentiality agreement exists between Comcastoffers.com and such third party.

If, and only if, you indicated during the application or registration process you'd like to receive advertising and promotional materials related to Comcastoffers.com, we may also use your Personal Information to send information from our media partners or service providers. On occasion, for example, we or our media partners and service providers may send you e-mail to introduce products or services that might be of interest to you. We may also use your Personal Information to keep in touch with you when necessary, for example, to send to you confirmation, rebuttal, shipment or reminder e-mail messages. If you identify yourself to us by sending us an e-mail with questions or comments, we may use your Personal Information to respond to your questions or comments. (We may also file your comments for future reference.) You may opt-out of receiving e-mail at the time the request for your Personal Information is made at [comcastoptout@customerservicesite.com](mailto:comcastoptout@customerservicesite.com). In addition, e-mail will include instructions on how to unsubscribe.

We may also share Personal Information with our service providers and vendors. We will attempt to require that each of these service providers and vendors not use or disclose your Personal Information for any purpose other than providing you or us with products and services. However, we cannot guarantee their compliance with these restrictions. Comcastoffers.com does not sell Personal Information to third parties.

We reserve the right to provide or use your Personal Information in the following circumstances. We will release specific information about you or your account to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the Web Site, or a physical threat to you or others.

**Passively Collected Information and the Use of Cookie Technology**  
To help make our site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we invoke a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique, randomly generated number that temporarily resides on your computer. The cookie itself doesn't actually identify the visitor, just the particular computer session that a visitor uses to access our Web site. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself, we won't know who you are, even if we generate a cookie for your particular Web-site session. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply.

We use cookies to help us tailor our Web site to your needs, to deliver a better, more personalized service, and to remember certain choices you've made so you don't have to re-enter them. We may use cookies to track the pages on our Web site visited by our users, for example. We can build a better Web site if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to our Web site. 

In connection with the standard operation of Comcastoffers.com's systems, certain non-personally identifiable information about visitors to this Web site is recorded. This information is used primarily to tailor and enhance visitors' experience using the Web site. We may use this information in an aggregate, non-personally identifiable form to, among other things, measure the use of our Web site and determine which products and services are the most popular with Web-site visitors. 

We may share aggregate demographic/statistical information with our media partners, service providers and other third parties. In addition, Comcastoffers.com may allow some of our advertisers to display ads which solicit or contain technology to collect information about users.

**Privacy of Children**  
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Neither the Comcastoffers.com Web Site nor Comcastoffers.com's activities are intended for or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect Personal Information from any person we actually know is a child under the age of 13.

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
Our Web Site contains links to other Web sites operated by third parties that may be of interest to you. However, we do not and cannot control the information and content or links contained on these sites. We do not and cannot control the way in which these Web sites collect and/or use your Personal Information. Therefore, Comcastoffers.com disclaims any liability for any third party's use of your Personal Information obtained through using the third party Web site.

**Access to Personal Information**  
Please note that certain information transmitted to Comcastoffers.com may not be later modified or retrieved by Comcastoffers.com. However, at your request, we will use reasonable efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information (if we still retain it) and to revise, update or replace Personal Information that you inform us is in error. Please send us an e-mail at [comcastoptout@customerservicesite.com](mailto:comcastoptout@customerservicesite.com) to request access to any Personal Information that we have may have retained about you in our user database, to request a change in your Personal Information and/or to request us to inform our service providers of changes in your Personal Information. We cannot guarantee the actions of our service providers after we inform them of any changes. 

Certain Personal Information may be stored indefinitely so that Broadbandoffers.com can access data for any customer service issue as well as report on aggregate data.

**Opt-Out**  
Comcastoffers.com provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Comcastoffers.com at the point where information is requested of you. You also have the following options to prevent future communications from Comcastoffers.com:

  1. You can send an e-mail to [comcastoptout@customerservicesite.com](mailto:comcastoptout@customerservicesite.com).
  2. You can select "UNSUBSCRIBE" upon receiving an e-mail communication. 
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address:  

> **Comcastoffers.com**  
>  1555 Sherman Avenue  
>  Box 310  
>  Evanston, Illinois   
>  60201  
>  ATTN: Director of Technology 

©2007 ComcastOffers.com. All rights reserved.
